m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：紫杉 珞珞珞小娘 vitaminwater janiceyj 狂舞之鹤 静妹粒
翻译：板扎小早 王二川 持久君 卫管小色盲 NO.Zero
时间轴： 面条打包子  NO.Zero  后期：、青衣
校对：紫杉  面条打包子     总监：紫杉
罗素在哪儿
Where's Russell?
-他在规划室  -知道了
- He's in layout. - Okay.
-怎么了  -罗素
- What's going on? - Russell?
罗素
Russell.
-萨拉出事了  有枪战  -有多严重
- It's Sara. There's been a shooting. - How bad is it?
-我不确定  她手机没信号  -芬恩怎么样
- I-I don't know. Her cell phone cut out. - What about Finn?
-也联系不上  -听我说
- I can't reach her either. - Listen to me,
打电话到拉克斯顿的治安办公室
I want you to call the Sheriff's Office in Larkston.
问问看他们是否掌握枪击的具体情况
Find out if they know anything about the shooting.
快去
Go.
吉姆  我是D.B.
Jim, it's DB.
我要用直升机
I need a chopper.
副警长死了
Deputy's dead.
警长还活着
Sheriff's still alive.
萨拉
Sara.
这四十八个小时很不好过吧  你还好吗
It's been a rough 48 hours. You all right?
我没事儿
I'm okay.
只是被子弹擦伤了
Bullet just grazed me.
芬恩呢  知道她在哪儿吗
What about Finn-- do you know where she is?
不知道  她不接电话
No, I don't know. She's not picking up her cell.
如果他追杀她怎么办
What if he went after her?
那么...
Well...
就要尽快找到她
we gotta find her.
拜托  停一停啊
Hey! Come on! Stop!
《犯罪现场调查》  第十四季第十集
医护人员说你没事儿了
Paramedics said you're good to go.
布拉斯会带你去拉克斯顿的
So, Brass is gonna take your statement
治安办公室做笔录
down in the Sheriff's Office in Larkston.
我知道  找到芬恩后我马上就去
Yeah, yeah, I'll go over there as soon as we find Finn.
不不  听我说
No, no, listen to me, please--
关于过去几天发生的事
there are gonna be a lot of questions
他们肯定有很多疑问
about what happened the last couple of days.
萨拉  我需要你现在就和布拉斯说清楚
Sara, I need you to talk to Brass now-- please.
尼克和我会继续待在这儿
Nick and I are gonna stay here
寻找芬恩  你放心
until we find Finn, I promise you that.
好吗
All right?
过来抱抱
Come here, let me...
真高兴你没事
I'm so glad you're okay.
-谢谢  -没事儿
- Thank you. - Yeah.
这里谁管事儿
Uh, who's in charge here, please?
现在应该是我了
I... I-I guess that would be me.
你好  我叫麦克辛·伦诺克斯
Yeah. Uh, Maxine Lennox.
伦诺克斯副警长  我是现场调查主管罗素
Deputy Lennox, I'm CSI Supervisor Russell.
我手下的一个调查员失踪了
One of my CSIs is missing.
她之前曾在这里调查一宗案件
She was investigating a case up here.
-她叫朱莉·芬恩利  -我知道
- Her name's Julie Finlay. - Yes.
几个小时前我在旅馆碰见她
I saw her a few hours ago at the motel.
还把我的车借给了她
Lent her my car.
她说她要跟进一条线索
She said she was following up on a lead.
她说去哪儿了吗
Did she say where she was going?
-没有  -我要你现在就去警用车上
- No. - I need you to put a broadcast out
-发布寻人通告  -好的先生
- on your car, right now. - Yes, sir.
请坐下  马上就会有人来负责
Have a seat. We'll be right with you.
给你带了这个  说不定有用
I got you this; I thought you could use it.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还撑得住吗
How you holding up?
这几天不太好过
It's been a long couple of days.
我知道你现在不是状态  还很担心
Well, uh, I know things might be a little cloudy for you
但是我必须...
right now, but, uh...
对于这里发生的事情
You know, we have to officially
必须得有一份官方记录
get a statement to know what happened up here.
这规矩我懂
I know the drill.
那我们就从头开始吧
Let's start from the beginning.
你和另两位现场调查员芬恩还有布洛迪
What were you and CSIs Finlay and Brody
在拉克斯顿做什么
doing here in Larkston?
我们原本没想来拉克斯顿
Larkston was never part of the plan.
我们只是想好好享受一下  毕竟…
We just wanted to have a little fun, I mean...
我们多久没有整个周末都放假了
how often do we all have the weekend off?
四十八小时前
我准备回家  开瓶红酒
Whew! I am gonna go home, open a bottle of wine
看赫本和特雷西的经典[美国四十年代荧屏情侣]
and watch Hepburn and Tracy movies.
我也想啊
Oh, wish I could do that.
可是我堆了好多衣服没洗呢
I've got about a month's worth of laundry to do.
摩根  你有什么打算
What are you up to, Morgan?
我准备去里诺
Uh, actually, I am driving to Reno.
我妈给了我张水疗馆的礼券
My mom got me this gift certificate for a spa there.
那里有所有基于矿物的治疗
It has all mineral-based treatments,
所以我要去做紫水晶按摩
so I am getting the amethyst massage.
它应该可以安神
It's supposed to calm the nerves
还能吸走点负能量
and absorb negative energy.
我挺需要的
I could probably use that.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
你们应该跟我一起去
You guys should join me.
我有个套房
I got a suite.
地方够大
Got plenty of room.
我们不想毁了你的周末
Oh, I... I mean, we don't want to crash your weekend.
开什么玩笑  你们能来当然好啦
Are you kidding? I would love it.
我讨厌一个人喝酒
I hate drinking alone.
按摩  美酒
Massages, alcohol...?
算我一个
I'm in.
我也去
太棒了  好吧  我们回家换衣服
Awesome! Okay... um, let's go home, change,
然后一小时后在这见
and I'll meet you back here in an hour.
-好吧  -好
- Okay. - Okay.
但是你们没能到里诺
But you never made it to Reno.
为什么呢
Why not?
芬恩说如果我们坐她的车
Finn said that if we took her car,
我们半小时内就能到
we could make it there in half the time.
结果证明那是个错误
That turned out to be a mistake.
这车真不错
Yeah, she's a beauty.
-你装了个440型号的  -对
- You got the 440 in there? - Yeah.
还有四缸汽化器
And the four barrel carb.
那可是很大的马力啊
That's a lot of power.
我觉得我驾驭它毫无压力
Oh, I think I can handle it.
达瑞尔  车到底坏成什么样了
So, Darryl, uh, what's the bottom line?
-你能修好吗  -可以  只是水箱漏了
- Can you fix it? - Uh, yeah, it's just a broken water pump.
我可以在一小时内换好
I can replace it in about an hour.
如果我今晚订零件的话
Now, if, uh... I order the part tonight,
明天中午之前就能拿到
I should have it by noon tomorrow.
我们月光下的盐浴要报销了
So much for our moonlit salt scrubs.
我可以载你们去拉克斯顿
I can give you ladies a lift into Larkston.
没有水疗馆  但我们有个不错的小旅馆
We don't have a spa, but we do have a nice motel.
而且今晚是仙人掌酒吧的K歌之夜
Plus it's karaoke night at the Cactus.
太棒了
Awesome.
走吧
Come on.
喝一杯  吃点东西  很有意思的
Have a drink, some food, it'll be fun.
笑得嘴都咧开了  你们这些家伙
Try not to look so happy, you guys.
天呐  两杯龙舌兰下肚
Oh, my gosh, couple shots of tequila
你就变成詹尼斯·乔普林[摇滚女歌手]了
and you turn into Janis Joplin.
我觉得你没听到欢呼声
Yeah, I think you missed your calling.
-比如  太棒了  -谢谢
- Like, awesome! Wow! - Thanks. Yeah, uh, well,
其实我在大学里修了双专业
I was a double major in college.
化学和声乐  最终选了化学
Chemistry and voice. Chose chemistry.
但我在洛克希酒吧的一个乐队当过一年主唱
But I was the front woman for a band at The Roxy for a year.
真不敢相信我们居然不知道这些
I can't believe we didn't know this about you.
说到秘密
Speaking of secrets,
我不知道你还对机械有兴趣
I didn't know you were into mechanics.
是啊  你和达瑞尔
Yeah, you and, um, Darryl...
看起来很享受彼此今晚的陪伴
seem to be enjoying each other's company tonight.
他很好  他其实很聪明
He's very nice. He's, uh, he's actually smart.
他很有趣
He's, uh, he's funny.
对车了解得很多
Knows a lot about cars.
那他怎么还一个人喝酒  太可惜了
Oh. It's too bad he's so unattractive.
这些是达瑞尔请的
This round's on Darryl.
-谢谢你  -谢谢
- Thank you. - Oh, thank you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这杯敬姑娘们的周末
All right, here's to our girls' weekend.
对
Yes.
-天呐  -太爽了
- Oh, God. - Aah. Whee.
我要回旅馆去了
All right, so I'm gonna, um, go back to the motel.
别走啊  我点了一首碧昂丝的歌
No, I-I put in a Beyonce's song,
我们一起唱吧
I want us all to sing it together.
我跟你一起去
I'll come with you.
-喂  -不用
- Hey. - No, stay.
不用了  自己玩得开心点
Stay, have fun.
达瑞尔会带我回去
Darryl's gonna walk me home.
我俩的话儿还没说完呢
We need to finish the conversation.
-原来如此  -当然
-Uh huh.  - Of course you do.
待会儿见
See you guys later.
好的  祝你玩得开心
Okay. Have fun.
必须的
Yeah, right.
碧昂丝是谁
Who's Beyonce?
这儿夜空的星星真漂亮
Stars are really beautiful out here.
维加斯的灯光太多了
There's so many lights in Vegas, you know,
从来看不到星星
you never get to see them.
见多了我都不怎么注意到它们了
Yeah, I guess I don't really notice them anymore.
我生长在此
Born and raised here.
会觉得这一切都是理所当然
I guess I kind of take them for granted.
在这里长大是不是很棒
Was it great growing up here?
对  挺不错的
Yeah, it was great.
-真的吗  -真的很棒
- Was it? - It was real great.
一定不错
Must have been.
你裤兜里有东西
You have something in your pocket.
你指的是...
You mean, um...
你指的是这个
you mean this.
被你发现了
You got me.
我不喜欢已婚的男人
I'm not really into married men.
也不喜欢骗子
Or liars.
我现在没再撒谎了
I'm not lying anymore.
但你还是有妇之夫
You're still married.
可我婚姻不幸福
Not happily.
晚安
Good night.
Night?
知道吗  你真是会戏弄人
You're a little tease, you know that?
达瑞尔  别这样
Darryl, don't do this.
你哪儿也别想去
Not going anywhere.
你以为你可以勾引我一整晚
You think you can just lead me on
然后头也不回地走开吗
all night and then just walk away?
别这样
Don't do this.
我不想伤害你
I don't want to hurt you.
可我下得了手
But I will.
你死定了
You're dead.
发生什么事了
What happened?
天呐
Oh, my God,
-你流血了  -我用刀捅了他
- you're bleeding. - I stabbed him.
-你在说什么  -他攻击了我
- What are you talking about? - He attacked me.
-什么  -我觉得他死了
- What? - I think he's dead.
达琳  快去叫警长
Darlene, call the sheriff.
芬恩  发生什么事了
Finn, what happened?
我也不清楚
I don't know.
我们得带你去医院  你需要缝针
Okay, we gotta get you to a hospital -- you need stitches.
我不想去医院
I don't want to go to the hospital.
达琳在哪儿
Where's Darryl?
-他就在那边  -带我们去看看
- He's-he's over here. - Show us.
他人原先就在这儿
His body was right here.
跑哪儿去了
Where'd it go?
-你捅了他几次  -两次
- How many times did you stab him? - I stabbed him twice.
刀呢  你怎么处理的
What did you do with the knife?
我就把刀丢在他身边了
Uh, I-I-I dropped it beside the body.
或许你没杀死他  芬恩
Right, maybe you didn't kill him, Finn.
他或许还没死  你检查他脉搏了吗
Maybe he's not dead. Did you take his pulse?
没有  我只是想着要逃跑
No, no, I wanted to get away.
可我确定当时他一动也不动了
I-I'm sure he was not moving.
没事的  听到了吗
It's okay. All right?
一切都会好起来的
It's gonna be all right.
好
All right.
并非专用标签  但至少可以用
They're not flags, they'll have to do.
看不出他流了多少血
Really hard to tell how much blood he lost.
全渗进泥土里了
It seeped into the dirt.
这儿有从那滩血那里延伸过来的血迹
There are blood drops moving away from the blood pool.
芬恩  达瑞尔穿的是牛仔靴吗
Hey, Finn, was Darryl wearing cowboy boots?
是啊
Yeah.
这儿有鞋印
I got a boot print
还有对应的血迹
and corresponding blood drops.
他当时站着  在流血
He was on his feet and bleeding.
他没死  他还能走
Ah, I didn't kill him. He walked away.
这儿还有第二组鞋印  看来
There's a second set of prints, so...
他不是独自一人  有人帮忙
not by himself. Somebody helped him.
帮他上了车
Into a car.
血迹到轮胎印这儿
Blood drops end...
就没有了
where these tire tracks begin.
你们这几个姑娘在搞什么呢
What the hell you girls think you're doing?
别担心
It's all right.
警长  我们是执法部门的
Sheriff, we're law enforcement--
拉斯维加斯犯罪现场调查员
Las Vegas CSIs
赛德尔  芬恩利和布洛迪
Sidle, Finlay and Brody.
拉斯维加斯犯罪实验室的
Las Vegas Crime Lab?!
我没请你们出现场啊
I didn't call you to work this scene.
我们不是来出现场的
Uh, we're not working the scene.
我们这位朋友被袭击了
Our friend here was attacked.
我接到的电话说是你把他杀了
I got a phone call saying you killed him.
有证据表明达瑞尔还活着
Well, the evidence shows that Darryl is still alive.
证据
Evidence?
你们不是说你们不是来出现场的吗
Thought you said you weren't working the scene.
我们真不是来出现场的
We're not working the scene.
我们就是四处看看
We just made a couple of observations.
是嘛
Yeah.
行  我也来看看
Yeah, I'm making a few of those myself.
三个姑娘  喝了酒
Three girls; been drinking...
一个在流血  在非工作的犯罪现场
one bleeding... messing around
乱晃捣乱
in a crime scene you got no business being in.
我们不是在捣乱
We're not messing around.
我怎么知道你是不是把人杀了
How do I know you didn't kill him?
把尸体丢弃在其他地方
Dumped his body somewhere.
现在又来破坏证据
Now you're tampering with the evidence.
-然后他把你们放了  -没有
- So he just released you? - No.
没有  他手下把我和摩根分开
No. His deputies separated Morgan and I,
在酒吧里问了我们话
and, uh, they interrogated us inside the bar.
芬恩呢
What about Finn?
警长把她软禁在了汽车旅馆里
Sheriff put her under house arrest in the motel.
芬恩说他对她进行了盘问
Finn said that he grilled her
当时医生在给她缝伤口
while the local doctor stitched her up.
你是说那把匕首
So you're saying the knife...
是达瑞尔的
was Darryl's?
是的
Yes.
那怎么到了你手里
How'd it end up in your hands?
我跟你说了
I told you:
他拔出匕首
He pulled the knife,
想要强奸我
he tried to rape me,
我夺下了匕首
I grabbed the knife
奋力抵抗
and I fought back.
看看这些伤痕  警长
Look at these bruises, Sheriff.
是挣扎过的痕迹
Consistent with a struggle.
所以你出于自卫捅了他
So you stabbed him in self-defense
然后就在你回酒吧告诉你朋友的
and in that few minutes, while you were inside the bar
那几分钟里
telling your friends,
-有人把达瑞尔和匕首都带走了  -是的
- someone took Darryl and the knife. - Yes.
他正在哪儿躲着呢  我觉得
And he is out there, and I-I think
你应该去找他
you should be out there looking for him.
我已经派手下去他家和他的汽修厂了
Oh, I got deputies going to his house and his auto shop.
不过  说真的
But, frankly...
你就行行好  省下彼此的时间
you could save us all a lot of time.
坦白吧
Just tell us the truth.
我说的都是实话
I am telling you the truth.
我是犯罪现场调查员
I am a CSI,
我总能享受无罪推定的权利
and I deserve the benefit of the doubt.
我认识达瑞尔·沃尔什有十五年了
I've known Darryl Walsh for 15 years.
我每周四都和他一起打扑克
I play poker with him every other Thursday.
他不像会做这种事的人
It just doesn't seem like something he'd do.
这些伤口又不是芬恩利女士自己弄上去的
Ms. Finlay didn't inflict these wounds herself.
可以了欧文  她今晚够受的了
Come on, Owen, she's been through enough.
你真要把她像犯人一样关在这儿吗
Do you really have to keep her locked up here like a prisoner?
没查清楚达瑞尔怎么样之前
Until I figure out what happened to Darryl...
她哪儿都不能去
she's not going anywhere.
你有你的职责  马蒂  我也是
You do your job, Marty; I'll do mine.
包扎好了
All done.
你会没事的
You're gonna be just fine.
谢谢
Thanks.
芬恩有消息吗
Any sign of Finn?
没有
No.
罗素刚发了短信
Russell just texted,
他们还在追查线索
they're still following up on leads.
犯罪现场调查员布洛迪给现场拍照
So, CSI Brody took photographs of the crime scene
因为你相信达瑞尔·沃尔什还活着
which you believe prove that Darryl Walsh was still alive.
你把照片给为你做笔录的
Now, did you share those photos with the deputies
-警官了吗  -那是当然
- who questioned you? - Yes. Of course.
现场不由我们负责
I mean, it wasn't our scene.
法律上我们有责任转交给他们
We were legally obligated to turn 'em over.
可摩根没有删除她手机里的那些照片对吗
But Morgan didn't delete them from her cell phone, did she?
胎面宽度   找到匹配
拉斯维加斯警局车辆数据库
品牌  布里奇曼2008
型号  P235/70R18
宽度  8.00
花纹深度 12.00
轮胎典型适用  种类  福特卡车
萨拉
-你好  格雷格  -你们发给我的
- Hey, Greg. Hey. That, uh, tire track photo
现场的轮胎印  我用胎面搜索系统
that you guys sent me from the crime scene, I ran it through
查过了  轮胎是布里奇曼牌
Treadfind-- tire was manufactured
2008年制造的
by Bridgman Wheels in 2008.
-是什么车的轮胎  -其实是卡车
- What kind of car? - A truck, actually.
主要用于福特皮卡轻骑兵以及福特F150
Primarily the Ford Ranger and F-150.
我调出了车管所的记录  这就给你发送
I pulled DMV records. Sending you a list
所有拉克斯顿地区
of everyone in Larkston
有这种车的车主清单
who owns that vehicle.
收到了  谢谢
Pulling it up now. Thank you.
-警长  -什么事
- Hey, Sheriff? - Yeah.
根据车管所的记录
According to DMV records,
镇上有三十几辆车的轮胎印
there's over 30 vehicles in this town with tires
与我们在现场发现的吻合
that match the tracks that we found at the crime scene.
我只知道
Well, the last I checked,
你们并不参与此案的调查
you weren't part of this investigation.
警长  证据显示
Sheriff, evidence shows
有人帮达瑞尔·沃尔什上了一辆卡车
that somebody helped Darryl Walsh into a truck.
我们找到那辆车  也许就能找到达瑞尔·沃尔什
We find the truck, maybe we find Darryl.
调查员芬恩利就清白了
It exonerates CSI Finlay.
你们真以为他还活着
You really think he's still alive?
现场没有拖拽的痕迹
There were no drag marks.
鞋印和血迹说明
Boot prints and blood drops show
他自己站起来  走上了那辆车
that he was upright and moving when he got into the truck.
你搜过他家  也搜过他工作的地方
You've searched his home, you've searched his work.
都没有他的踪影
You haven't found him.
这份清单是我们最靠谱的线索了
This list is the closest thing we have to a lead.
我们只想请你看看
All we're asking is that you take a look at it.
看清单上有没有谁可能
Is there anyone on here that might
为了达瑞尔两肋插刀的
put themselves on the line for Darryl?
好吧
All right.
瓦莱丽·尔文  达瑞尔的妻子
Valerie Irvin, Darryl's wife.
-很好  我们去会会她  -办不到
- Great. Let's go talk to her. - We can't.
今早她去了维加斯
She left for Vegas this morning.
我这就打给格雷格
I'll call Greg right away.
让格雷格带她到局里问话
Have him bring her in for questioning.
你看来并不是很担心
You don't seem too worried
你丈夫  尔文女士
about your husband, Mrs. Irvin.
我是说  达瑞尔身受刀伤
I mean, Darryl was stabbed.
人还不见了
Now he's missing.
你却在维加斯玩老虎机
And you're playing slots in Vegas.
他会现身的
Oh, he'll turn up.
他总这样
He always does.
他以前也玩过失踪
So he's gone missing before?
我们又不会总是黏着对方
We don't really keep tabs on each other.
达瑞尔有他要做的事
Darryl does his thing,
我也一样
I do mine.
昨晚达瑞尔被刺伤之后  拉克斯顿有人
Uh, last night, after Darryl was stabbed, back in Larkston,
把他从旅馆接走了
somebody picked him up from the motel.
反正不是我
Wasn't me.
我在餐厅工作了整晚  晚六点到早六点
I was working all night at the diner, 6:00 to 6:00.
下了班我就直接开车来这儿了
I drove straight here after my shift.
我们搜查了你的车
Uh, we searched your truck.
发现这东西
Found this...
留在地毯上
stuck to the floor mat.
那是什么
What is that?
是一片树脂含量很高的叶子
It was a high resin leaf,
还有膨胀粘土块
along with expanded clay pebbles.
是大麻
Marijuana.
我明白了  达瑞尔正偷偷地
I get it-- so Darryl was running a hydroponic
在无土栽培大麻
pot-growing operation under the radar.
说到无土栽培
Thing about hydroponics--
这可相当费电
it requires a lot of energy.
我找到了拉克斯顿城的电网用电量
I pulled up the electrical grid of the town of Larkston.
蓝色的点代表家庭平均每月的用电量
The blue dots represent average household electrical use per month,
大约是九百千瓦
about 900 kilowatts.
它们都是蓝点
Well, they're all blue dots.
种植大麻至少要用到那五倍的电量
A grow house would use at least five times that much power.
现在  和我一起
Now, step back in time with me
跟着电流回到过去
as we follow the current back to the past.
这是去年城里的月用电量回顾
This is a time lapse reversal of the town's electrical use over the past year.
那就是你要的红点
There's your red dot--
说明四个月内的用电量超过了五千千瓦
indicates usage of over 5,000 kilowatts a month for four months.
之后一个月内恢复正常
Goes back to normal for a month
之后的四个月又涨回去
and then spikes again for another four months.
典型的大麻生长和收获周期
Typical growth and harvest cycle for marijuana.
四个月生长  一个月晒干
Four months to grow, one month to dry.
但只能享受几分钟
And only minutes to enjoy it.
我听说是这样的
So I've heard.
那是什么  一栋房子吗
So what is that, a house?
根据卫星图像来看
Well, according to the satellite image,
是一个破旧的谷仓
it's a dilapidated barn,
登记在伊迪丝·斯金纳名下
registered to Edith Skinner.
她都八十五岁了
She's 85.
内华达  拉克斯顿  巴罗路  登记所有人  伊迪丝·斯金纳  出生日期  1928年5月25
你觉得老斯金纳女士会知道
Think old lady Skinner has any idea
达瑞尔和瓦在她的谷仓里做了什么吗
what Darryl and Val are doing in her barn?
我刚跟她通过电话
I just talked to her.
达瑞尔告诉她在这停放了几辆车
Darryl told her he was storing some cars here.
把那东西收起来
Put that thing away.
达瑞尔可能就藏在这里的某个角落
Darryl could be hiding in here somewhere.
我不会冒任何险的
I'm not taking any chances.
威利斯  打开后车厢
Willis, pop the trunk.
他不是你想像中的那种怪物
He's not the monster you're making him out to be.
无意冒犯  警长
No offense, Sheriff,
但你可能并不像你认为的那样了解达瑞尔
but I'm not sure you know Darryl the way you think you do.
都不是本州车牌
Plates are all from out of state.
达瑞尔可能是为了它们的零件才买的
Well, Darryl could've bought 'em for spare parts.
也有可能除了培养大麻外
Or, in addition to growing pot,
他还开了家地下拆车厂
he's running a chop shop.
他不在这里
No sign of him.
警长  副警长  看看这个
Sheriff, Deputy, take a look at this.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你还认为你的朋友不是个怪物吗
You still think your friend's not a monster?
好了  我们开始吧
All right. Let's do it.
好了
All right.
头部和脸上有钝器挫伤
Blunt force trauma to the head and face.
前臂有复合型骨折
Compound fracture to the right forearm.
看上去她是被殴打致死
It looks like she was beaten to death.
当我作验尸官时
When I have to put on my coroner's hat,
死因一般都是自然死亡或者车祸
death is usually natural causes or car accidents.
很少看到这种暴力致死的
Don't see violence like this very often.
真希望我们也能这么说
Wish we could say the same.
没有证件
No identification.
她的鞋子上有点绿色的残留物
There's a green residue on the shoes here-- hmm.
不是从车里来的
Didn't come from the car.
我能采一下样吗
Do you mind if I collect it?
没问题
Not at all.
没有新鲜的血液
There's no fresh blood.
没有迹象表明达瑞尔昨晚来过这儿
There's no evidence that Darryl was here last night.
已核实过他妻子的供词
Wife's alibi checked out.
带他走的人并不是瓦
Val wasn't the one that picked him up.
可能是他的朋友载了他一程
Maybe one of his buddies gave him a ride,
并把他藏在某处
and he's hiding him somewhere.
瓦说她根本不知道达瑞尔在这儿做的事
Val said that she had no idea what Darryl was doing up here.
她说他成天借她的车
Said that he borrows her truck all the time.
这样她车里的石块和大麻叶就解释的通了
It could explain the pebbles and the cannabis.
我去查一下这些车的牌照和登记资料
I'll run the license and registration on these vehicles.
看能否查到车主信息
See if we can figure out who they belong to.
谢谢你  警长
Thanks. Uh, Sheriff...
我非常希望你能让现场调查员芬恩利过来帮忙
I would really like CSI Finlay to help us out on the case.
现在没有理由再把她关在酒店房间里
There's no reason to keep her locked up in that motel room.
但她的确捅了达瑞尔
She still stabbed Darryl.
那是出于正当防卫
In self-defense.
但她和这个犯罪现场毫无瓜葛
But she had nothing to do with this crime scene,
而且坦白说
and frankly...
我们确实需要她的帮助
we could really use her help.
好吧
Fine.
我会撤销软禁令  但是她不能离开镇子
I'll lift the house arrest, but she's not leaving town.
还有一件事
One more thing...
有没有人说过你有点得寸进尺
Anyone ever tell you you're pushy?
我需要在场所有人的DNA样品
I just need DNA samples from everyone here,
以便从检验结果中排除
for elimination purposes.
什么  你觉得我们之间有人与此案有关吗
What, you think one of us had something to do with this?
只是走个程序
Just procedure.
然后呢
Then what happened?
摩根带着那些样品回到实验室
Morgan took those samples back to the lab.
那尸检呢  是由金尼医生负责吗
What about the body-- did Dr. Kinney do the autopsy?
不是的
No. No.
鉴于他在法医病理学上经验有限
Because of his limited experience in forensic pathology,
摩根就把尸体也带回了拉斯维加斯
Morgan took the body back to Vegas as well.
交给大卫·菲利普斯处理
She handed it off to David Phillips.
让我理一理
So, let me get this straight.
芬恩  摩根和萨拉本来打算周末出去玩
Finn, Morgan and Sara go away for a nice fun weekend,
结果芬恩遭遇袭击
Finn is then attacked,
被控谋杀  萨拉还找到另一具尸体
accused of murder and Sara finds a body?
没错
Yeah.
和她们预想的轻松假期大相径庭
Not the relaxing weekend they were hoping for.
大卫  地中海酒店发现一具尸体
Hey, David, there's a 419 at the Mediterranean.
我去看看
I'm on it.
死者指甲上画着南瓜
Pumpkins painted on her nails.
看来她很热衷于万圣节
Must've liked Halloween.
她可能就是那时失踪的
That could be when she went missing.
我去给她的手指补补水
I'll rehydrate her fingertip,
看能不能查到身份信息
see if we can get an I.D.
基于环境温度和尸体的情况
Based on the temperature of the building and the condition of the body,
死亡时间不超过一个月
I'd say she's been dead less than a month.
这像是勒痕
These look like ligature marks.
伤痕很细
Narrow.
凶手应该是用绳子将她捆住
Killer could've used a string to tie her up.
可能是电线
Maybe wire.
死者生前遭到捆绑和殴打
Restrained and beaten.
圆形伤口的形状和尺寸说明
Circular size and shape tell me
她是被锤子打死的
she was hit repeatedly with a hammer.
能看出来她的年龄吗
Any idea how old she was?
智齿已经张全  超过十八岁
Wisdom teeth are present, so she's over 18.
她牙齿上沾着点东西
And there's something in her teeth.
帮我拿一下手电
Could you hold that?
看起来像是阴毛
Looks like a pubic hair.
说明临死前还有性行为
Suggests sexual activity close to the time of death.
考虑到她曾被捆住手脚
Considering that she was restrained,
我敢说这事肯定不是你情我愿
I'm betting the sex wasn't consensual.
我去做一套性侵犯检查
I'll collect an SAE kit.
毛囊还未脱落
Follicle is still attached.
应该能提取出DNA
Should be able to get DNA.
也许能帮我们查到凶手
Might help us identify her killer.
你查到什么了
What did you find out?
死者名叫布伦达·惠特克
Victim's name is Brenda Whittaker.
二十三岁  来自圣地亚哥
She is a 23-year-old from San Diego.
四个月前失踪
Disappeared four months ago.
交叉比对过她的驾照和车辆注册信息
Cross-referenced her driver's license and registration
以及指纹  证明死者就是她
and prints confirmed it was her.
罗素
生前被囚禁并强奸
Held against her will and raped.
我们从她口部  肛门以及阴道中
Spermatozoa was found in the oral, anal and vaginal samples
布伦达·惠特克
均发现精子痕迹
collected from the victim.
DNA检测结果还未出来
Still waiting on the DNA.
这结果足以证明达瑞尔是个杀人凶手
Which will prove Darryl's a murderer.
不敢相信他还逍遥法外
Can't believe he's still out there.
所以你最好小心点
Which is why you better watch your back.
说说谷仓里其他几辆车的情况
Tell me about the other cars in the barn.
是另外两名失踪女性的车
They belong to two other missing women.
来自塞多纳的十九岁大学生
A 19-year-old college student from Sedona
艾普利·丹尼斯  佩内洛普·万斯
还有来自盐湖城的二十八岁女招待
and a 28-year-old waitress from Salt Lake City--
她们都独自旅行  失踪一年以上
both missing for over a year and both traveling alone.
达瑞尔是个修理工  对吧
Darryl's a mechanic, right?
没错  他开了家加油站还有一间修理厂
Yeah, he operates a gas station and a garage.
那么也许这几个女人车坏了  或者去加油
So maybe these women had car trouble, stopped for gas.
正好又是达瑞尔的菜
Just happened to be Darryl's type.
他就引诱她们  绑架她们
He seduced them, abducted them,
强奸她们  也许还杀了她们
raped them, and probably killed them.
目前只找到了布伦达·惠特克的尸体
Brenda Whittaker was the only one found.
其他几具尸体肯定被达瑞尔抛尸他处了
Darryl must've dumped the other bodies someplace else.
霍奇斯打电话来了  我得挂了
Oh, hey. This is Hodges. I have to go.
大卫·霍奇斯
工作
挂吧
Oh, go ahead.
有什么发现吗
What have you got?
检测了摩根从受害者鞋上收集的东西
Trace Morgan collected from the victim's shoes--
短棘盘星藻
pediastrum boryanum.
藻类
Algae?
只在淡水中生长的绿色藻类
Specifically green algae found in fresh water.
我查了下
I did some checking,
最近的淡水水体也在二百四十公里外了
and the nearest large body of fresh water is over 150 miles away.
这不可能啊
That doesn't make any sense.
昨晚我们通电话的时候  芬恩就在这儿
Finn was here when we spoke on the phone last night,
所以她最后就是出现在这
so this is the last place she was seen.
而且就是
And that was...
几小时前
a few hours ago.
我们知道她借了副警长的车
Well, we know she borrowed the Deputy's car.
她要去哪
Where was she going?
她哪都不该去的
She shouldn't have been going anywhere.
管理员
她笔记本有密码
Her laptop's locked.
知道密码可能是什么吗
Any idea what the password might be?
血性女孩
Um... bloodgirl.
不对
Nope.
血性女孩528
Bloodgirl528?
密码错误
不对
No, sir. No.
对了  我想到了
Oh, I know, I know-- uh...
试试"爱格妮思"
Try "Agnes."
爱格妮思  是谁
Agnes? Who's that?
她深爱的疯阿姨
Crazy aunt she loved.
进去了
Worked. All right.
根据她的浏览记录
So, according to her Web history,
她在找这附近的淡水水体
she was looking for fresh bodies of water in the area.
她找到了吗
Did she find any?
没有  这上面看是没有
No, not according to this.
她在仙人掌烧烤酒吧的广告单上
She wrote the name "Gary" next to an ad
写了一个叫加里的名字
for the Diamond Cactus Bar & Grill.
那就是她们周五晚上去的那家酒吧
That's the bar they were at Friday night.
给他们打个电话
Give them a little call here.
你好
Uh, hey, there.
加里在吗
Um... is Gary around?
下班了是吗
He's on his break?
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
他是那个酒保
He's the bartender.
要是想了解镇上的信息
If I was looking for information around town,
我肯定第一个去问他
that'd be the first place I'd start.
我们去跟他谈谈
Yeah, let's go talk to him.
犯罪现场调查员芬恩利
Did CSI Finlay ask you
问了你关于淡水水体的事吗
anything about bodies of water?
问了
Yeah.
她想知道
She wanted to know
这附近有没有在地图上没被标记过的湖或者溪流
if there were any lakes or streams nearby that weren't on a map.
我能想到的只有岩石湖
Only thing I could think of was Stone Rock Lake.
是个人造湖吗
Is that a man-made lake?
现在只是个大坑了
Just a hole in the ground now.
好几年前就干了
It dried up years ago.
藻类还是能存活下来的
You know, the algae would still be there.
离这儿有多远
How far away is this place?
离这儿四十八公里
About 30 miles from here
就在旧的岩石湖露营地
in the old Stone Rock Lake campground.
就在史蒂文森高速边
Just off Stevenson Highway.
谢谢你  加里
Thanks, Gary.
你怎么看
What do you think?
我最讨厌查错方向了
I'd hate to go running off in the wrong direction.
我觉得那个废弃的露营地
Well, I think that an abandoned campground
是达瑞尔关押女性人质的绝佳场所
would be a great place for Darryl to hold women hostage.
也是个完美的藏身地
Be a good place for him to hide out, too.
芬恩在两个小时前就出发了
Finn's got a two-hour head start on us.
我们得赶在她找到达瑞尔之前找到她
Let's go find her before she finds him.
那怎么会最后变成枪战了呢
So how'd you end up in a nasty gunfight?
威利斯副警长说他得到消息
Deputy Willis said that he got a tip
有人看到达瑞尔的车停在路边
that Darryl's car had been spotted on the side of the road,
就在州际公路边上
just off the interstate.
所以我和警长一起去看看
So... I went with the sheriff to check it out.
达瑞尔
Darryl!
我是欧文
It's Owen!
马上下车
Get out of the vehicle!
我们持有武器  达瑞尔
We're armed, Darryl!
快  把手伸出来
Come on, show us your hands!
他不在车里
He's not here.
那个巴士站还在用吗
Is that bus stop still active?
对  在用
Yes, it is.
巴士是去哪儿的
Where does it go?
里诺市  但他可能已经在那乘上了飞机
Reno. But from there, he could've hopped a plane.
现在他可能在任何地方
He could be anywhere by now.
去用对讲机问下
Get on the radio and find out
最近经过这里的巴士是什么时候
when the last bus came through here.
亨利  怎么了
Hey, Henry, what's up?
你确定吗
Are you sure?
好  谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
我需要从拉克斯顿到里诺的巴士时刻表  谢谢
I need a bus schedule from Larkston to Reno, please.
你这是要干什么
What the hell are you doing?
放下武器
Drop your weapons.
警长  从威利斯副警长身边走开
Sheriff, step away from Deputy Willis.
警长
Sheriff...
除非你告诉我这是怎么回事  否则我不走
I'm not going anywhere until you tell me what the hell's going on.
谷仓女尸身上提取的精液
Got DNA results on semen
DNA检测结果已经出来了
recovered from the woman's body in the barn.
分别属于两名男性
There were two male contributors.
你是说有两名男性与那名女性的死有关吗
You telling me there was two men involved in that woman's death?
达瑞尔·沃尔什和西蒙·威利斯副警长
Darryl Walsh and Deputy Simon Willis.
什么  简直胡说八道
What? That's crazy.
赛德尔女士  这里一定有什么误会
Ms. Sidle, there's got to be some kind of mistake.
我同事对比过我在罪案现场
My colleague compared the samples of the DNA
从你和副警长身上取来的DNA样本
that I got off of you and your deputies at the crime scene.
不可能有错
No mistake.
西蒙
Simon,
你和那女人的死有没有关系
did you have anything to do with that woman's death?
没有  欧文  拜托  你清楚我的为人
No. Owen, come on, you know me.
你何不...
Why don't you...
何不先把枪放下
why don't you put the gun down,
我们再好好谈谈
we'll talk about it.
好吧
Okay.
幸好你只是擦伤了
You're lucky it was just a graze.
是啊
Yeah.
我设法联系到了摩根
I managed to get a call through to Morgan and...
不久支援就到了
shortly after that, help arrived.
你救了加德纳警长的命
You know, you saved Sheriff Gardner's life.
我收到了他做完手术的消息
I got a message that he's out of surgery.
他对事发时的描述与你一致
His version of the facts matches yours.
所以  我们这完事了吗
So, we're done?
我会向内务部提交一份报告
I'll just file a report with the IAB,
他们自有定夺
they'll make their determination,
但不会有事的
but I wouldn't sweat it.
谢谢你特地跑过来
Thank you for coming.
不客气  我应该的
You're welcome. Of course.
萨拉
Oh, hey, Sara?
怎么了
Yeah?
如果你有芬恩的消息  要告诉我
Let me know when you hear about Finn.
我会的
I will.
岩石湖欢迎您
车牌号对上了
Plate's a match.
和伦诺克斯副警长的车相符
Match Deputy Lennox's car,
芬恩一定在这附近
so Finn's got to be around here.
钥匙在车里
The keys are in it.
一定是车出故障了
She must've had car trouble.
发动机盘管线被切断了
Coil wires have been cut.
达瑞尔想把她困在这里
Darryl wanted to make sure she couldn't leave.
尼克  我在车里发现了血迹
Nick... I got blood in the car.
好的
Okay.
我们行动吧
Let's go.
去右边
Take the right.
芬恩
Finn?
我在这边发现了一具男尸
I got a body over here, man.
他是达瑞尔·沃尔什
It's Darryl Walsh.
子弹正中胸口
Shot in the chest.
他已经死透了
He's dead as a doornail.
好吧  那么
All right, so...
芬恩没死  那她到底在哪里
Finn's not dead, then where the hell is she?
显然  这里就是
Obviously, this is where...
他囚禁女孩们的地方
he kept the girls.
没错
Yeah.
看看这里有些什么
So what do we got here?
发现了一套配备齐全的强奸工具箱
Got a fully loaded rape kit.
三颗子弹壳
Three shells.
0.380英寸子弹壳  与芬恩的枪相符
380 casing-- same as Finn.
这是她的手机
It's her cell phone.
好吧  咱们来推理一下
All right, let-let's figure this out.
首先
Well, for starters,
斧柄全是血迹
we got an ax handle with blood all over it.
强奸工具箱是打开的
Rape kit's open.
她的手机挨着它
Her cell phone's right next to it,
也许当时她正想要拍下犯罪现场  对吗
so maybe she was trying to document the crime scene, right?
没错  他弄废了她的车
Yeah, he disables her car,
他在返回途中拿了这把斧子  然后
he grabs the handle on his way back inside, and just...
偷袭了她
ambushes her.
这肯定惹毛了她
And that would have pissed her off.
是的  没错  她肯定反击了
Yeah, yeah. She fought back, for sure.
这边墙上有两颗子弹
And there's two bullets in the wall right here.
所以她开了三枪...
So she gets off three shots--
前两枪打偏了  但是第三枪  天呐
two miss, but that third one, boy...
正中他的胸口
punched a hole in his chest.
血泊边缘呈液态  所以...
Blood pool is still liquid around the edges, so...
这肯定是不久前刚发生的
this couldn't have happened too long ago.
车已报废  她应该是步行离开
Car's dead, she's got to be on foot.
经过这次打斗后
After she makes it through this mess,
她可能径直走向大路了
she probably made a beeline for the road.
我需要你留在这儿处理犯罪现场
I need you to stay here and process this scene.
芬恩枪杀了这家伙
Finn shot the guy.
我们得处理好
We need to do this right.
我去找她
I'll go look for her.
好的
Okay.
芬恩
Finn?
我们找朱莉·芬恩利
We're looking for Julie Finlay.
她的房间就在拐角处
She's right around the corner.
罗素  她怎么样了
Russell... how is she?
血已经止住了
They were able to stop the bleeding.
她的脾破裂
She has a ruptured spleen,
两根肋骨被撞断  还有脑震荡
two broken ribs, and a concussion.
但她会好起来的
She's gonna be okay, though.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
医生们说
The doctors say that
她所受的创伤与车撞伤相吻合
her injuries are consistent with being hit by a car.
我去过那条路
I was out on that road.
并没有发现任何刹车痕迹
I didn't see any skid marks.
这是蓄意撞人
This was intentional.
达瑞尔·沃尔什和副警长威利斯都已经死了
Darryl Walsh and Deputy Willis are both dead.
还会是谁做的呢
Who else could be behind this?
我们会查清楚的
That's what we're gonna find out.
不如你们去检查她全身及其衣物
Why don't you go ahead and process her and her clothes.
看看能发现什么
See what we can find.
这些条状淤青是被汽车护栅撞的
So, these bruise lines were made by the grill of the car.
那这个圆圈是某种车辆标志吗
So, this circle, is that some sort of logo?
不知道  我试试看能否提高分辨率
I don't know. Let me see if I can enhance it.
"MMC"
"MMC"?
那是什么车
What kind of car is that?
那不是车的标志
That's not a car.
是种荣誉徽章
That's a badge of honor.
我曾在古董车展上碰到过一个家伙
I-I saw this guy on one of those antique car shows.
他只开一辆古董车  开了好多年
He had this old car, he drove it for years,
当里程数积满161万公里时
and when he hit a million miles,
他就能在车的格栅前装上一个徽章
he got an emblem to put on the grill of his car.
正在搜索
百万英里俱乐部
"Million Mile Club."
MMC
MMC.
这个俱乐部很高端
It's very exclusive.
内华达州  拉克斯顿
拉克斯顿镇上刚好有一位会员
And the town of Larkston has one member.
医生
Hey, Doc.
我能坐这吗
Mind if I join you?
有什么事吗
Wh-What's this about?
我看到你的车停在外面
Well, I saw your car parked out front.
看起来  它出过事故啊
Looks like it's... been in an accident.
真是太可惜了
Now, that'd be a real shame--
毕竟那辆车你开了那么长时间
you've been driving that car for a long time.
行驶距离超过了一百万英里[约160万公里]
You got over a million miles on it.
你还因此得到了一个很棒的格栅徽章
You even have that cool grill badge to prove it.
那东西真不错
Love that thing.
当你开车撞我朋友时
It also made quite an impression on my friend...
还在她身上留下了一个印记
when you hit her with your car.
这是场意外
It was an accident.
不  不是
No, it wasn't.
你蓄意谋杀调查员芬恩利
You tried to kill CSI Finlay
是为了掩盖自己龌蹉的秘密
to protect your nasty secret.
什么龌蹉的秘密
What nasty secret?
你是副警长威利斯和达瑞尔·沃尔什
That you're a part of Deputy Willis and Darryl Walsh's
绑架团伙中的一员
little rape club.
不是这样的
That's not true.
我找到了你去过岩石湖旁小屋的证据
I found evidence you were in the cabin in Stone Rock Lake.
我去那只是为了在调查员芬恩利刺伤达瑞尔后
I was only there to stitch up Darryl
去帮他缝合伤口
after CSI Finlay stabbed him.
副警长威利斯强迫我的
Deputy Willis forced me.
那强奸布伦达·惠特克也是他强迫的吗
Did he also force you to rape Brenda Whittaker?
得了吧  我是位犯罪现场调查员
Come on. I'm a CSI, man,
还是很优秀的一位
and a pretty good one.
你没想到我会在门前的垃圾桶里
You don't think I'm gonna find your dirty, nasty used condoms
找到那恶心的使用过的安全套吗
in the trash can out front?
上面全是DNA
DNA was all over them.
我是跟她发生过性关系
So, I had sex with her.
不  你强奸了她
No. You raped her.
还强行捆绑她长达数月
And tying a woman up against her will, for months,
然后一遍又一遍地强奸她
and raping her over and over and over again,
之后你用铁锤砸烂了她的头
and then, you bash her head in with a hammer,
把尸体藏在她车子的引擎盖下
and you dump her body in the hood of her car--
我想不说你都知道这是什么罪了吧
I don't think I need to tell you what that is.
她的死与我无关
I had nothing to do with her death.
都是达瑞尔和副警长威利斯干的
That was all Darryl and-and Deputy Willis.
他们已经死了
Well, they're gone.
只剩你来承担责任了
You're the one left holding the bag now.
我知道至少还有两个女人失踪
So, I know there are at least two other women missing.
她们的尸体在哪里
Where are their bodies?
我不知道  我...
I don't know. I...
达瑞尔说他会处理尸体的
Darryl said they took care of them.
我只是跟他们做爱罢了
All I did was have sex with those girls.
没做过伤害她们的事
I-I never did anything to hurt them.
你以为强奸算什么
What do you think rape is?
你心理真扭曲  金尼医生
You're a sick man, Dr. Kinney.
你需要帮助
You need some help.
现在你被捕了
And now you're under arrest.
你听到了
You heard the man.
起来吧  走吧
Come on, let's go.
你怎么样了
How you doing?
你还好吗  还需要药吗
You all right? Want some more drugs?
现在打的这种药就挺好的
I do like the ones I'm on.
我们差点以为要失去你了  朱尔斯
Thought we almost lost you there for a minute, Jules.
我都已经开始面试替代你的人了
I already started interviewing replacements.
真的吗  你以为这么轻易就能摆脱我吗
Yeah? You think you can get rid of me that easily?
想想总可以吧
We could always hope.
准备见更多的访客了吗
Up for more visitors?
我明天再打给你
I'll call you tomorrow.
好的
Okay.
我们没能去成水疗馆
So, we never made it to the spa.
至少能给你带点替代品
Thought we'd bring it to you.
谢谢
Thank you.
那你下个周末打算做什么
So what do you want to do next weekend?